Melich, Tanya M.; Papers apap079
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Organizations, 1958-2016; Undated; 9; 10.6 cubic ft.
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics—San Diego Conference, 1991 November (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 29)
  - Center for Information Resources Policy—Draft of "The U.S. Communication and Information Resources: International Implications", 1981 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 30)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, 1992 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 31)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives—"Developing the Agenda, Framing the Message: A round table for Pro-Choice Legislators", 1991 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 32)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives—Newsletters, 1994-1999 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 33)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives—Newsletter, "Alternatives", 1998-2000 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 34)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives—Reproductive Choice, 1990-1992 (Box 1 (9-Organizations), Folder 35-36)
  - Center for Policy Research, Inc.—"The Responsive Community", 1991 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 1)
  - Center for Population Options, 1990-1992 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 2)
  - Center for Public Advocacy Research, Inc.—"Corporate Institutes for Working Parents in New York City", 1983 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 3)
  - The Center for Reproductive Law and Policy, 1991-1993; Undated (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 4)
  - The Center for Reproductive Law and Policy—"Removing Barriers: Improving Choices", 1996 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 5)
  - The Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions—"A Center Occasional Paper: Center Report", 1970 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 6)
  - The Center the Study of Democratic Institutions—"A Center Occasional Paper," Vol. 1 no. 1 and 5, Vol2. No. 4, Vol. 3 No. 4, 1967; 1968; 1969; 1970 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 7)
  - The Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions—"The Center Magazine", 1968; 1970; 1971 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 8)
  - Center for War, Peace and the News Media, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 9)
  - Center for War, Peace and the News Media—Cold War, 1986-1989 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 10)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1986-1990 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 11)
  - Center for Women's Policy Studies—Affiliates Quarterly Report, 1996-2000 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 12)
  - Center on Law and Citizenship, 1981 December; Undated (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 13)
  - Center on Law and Citizenship, 1982 July-1982 August (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 14)
  - Center on Law and Citizenship, 1982 September (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 15)
  - Child Care Action Campaign—General Information, 1982-1992 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 16)
  - Children's Defense Fund, 1994 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 17)
  - Children's Defense Fund, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 18)
  - Choices: Women's Medical Center, Inc. "On the Issues", 1985-1987 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 19)
  - Citizens for a Sustainable Democracy, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 20)
  - Coalition for Choice, 1989-1994; Undated (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 21)
  - Coalition for School-based Primary Care, 1993-1995; Undated (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 22)
  - Commission on Human Rights—Annual Report, 1996 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 23)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women, 1982-1991 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 24)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women, 1987 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 25-26)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women—Legislative & Status Reports, 1984-1990; 1984-1986 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 27)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women—Libby Antarsh Committee, 1987 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 28-31)
  - Committee of Agriculture—"Hearings before the Committee on Agriculture, House of Representatives" (Part 1-3), 1966 (Box 2 (9-Organizations), Folder 32-33)
  - Committee on the Constitutional System, 1983-1987; Undated (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 1-2)
  - Committee on the Constitutional System—Workbook for Constitutional System Review, 1983-1984 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 3-5)
  - Committee on Government Operations—"Subcommittee of the Committee on Government Operations House of Representatives," (Parts 1, 2, 4), 1970 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 6-7)
  - Common Cause, 1980-1981; 1991 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 8)
  - Communication Consortium, 1988-1991 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 9)
  - Communication Consultants for Choice, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 10)
  - Communication Consultants for Choice—General Information, 1985; Undated (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 11)
  - Communication Consultants for Choice—Promotional Materials and Techniques, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 12)
  - Community Family Planning Council, 1990-1995; Undated (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 13)
  - Community Leadership Project of Washington University, Vol. 3, No. 5, Vol. 5 No. 4, 1966; 1968 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 14)
  - Community Works, Inc. "The Long Walk to Freedom 1900-1999", 2000 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 15)
  - Congressional Quarterly Service—Reports, 1962; 1967 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 16)
  - Coro, 1975-1996 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 17)
  - Democracy Project—Annual Report, 1984 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 18)
  - The Democrat Leadership Council—"The New Democrat", 2000 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 19)
  - Domestic Policy Association, 1985 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 20)
  - Ethics and Public Policy Center, 1977-1981; Undated (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 21-22)
  - Family Planning Advocates of New York State—"Religious Mergers & HMOS: The Hidden Crisis for Reproductive Health Care", 1997-1998 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 23)
  - Foreign Policy Association—"Great Decisions 1918", 1996 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 24)
  - Forum 98—21st Century—"Taking Action for Women in the 21st Century", 1998 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 25)
  - Girls Incorporated—"Girls Ink", 1997 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 26)
  - Grassroots Movement for Environmental Justice Center for Health, Environment and Justice—"Everyone's Backyard", 2001-2002 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 27)
  - Hager Sharp (Communications Firm), 1994 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 28)
  - Hastings Center, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 29)
  - The Initiative Committee for National Economic Planning, 1975 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 30)
  - Institute for Philosophy& Public Policy—Report, 1995 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 31)
  - The Institute for Corporate Diversity—"Diversity Monitor," Vol. 1, No 1, 3, 4, 2000 (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 32)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research, 1988-1996; Undated (Box 3 (9-Organizations), Folder 33-34)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research, 1993 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 1)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research—Quarterly Newsletters, 2000 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 2)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research—Research in Brief/Information Network News, 1993 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 3)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research—"Resources for Reproductive Rights Research", 1993 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 4)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research—"Unnecessary Losses: Costs to Americans of the lack of Family and Medical Leave", 1990 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 5)
  - Institute of Politics, 1991 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 6)
  - Institute of Politics—"Proceedings, 20th Anniversary Edition 1966-1986" (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 7)
  - International Women's Democracy Center, 1996 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 8)
  - International Women's Health Coalition, 1990 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 9)
  - International Women's Rights Action Watch—The Committee on the Elimination of Discrimination Against Women Report, 1986-1993 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 10)
  - International women's Rights Action Watch—Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 11)
  - International Women's Rights Action Watch— The Woman's Watch, 1987-1989 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 12)
  - International Women's Rights Action Watch— The Woman's Watch, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 13)
  - International Women's Rights Action Watch— The Woman's Watch, 1993-1994 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 14)
  - International Women's Rights Action Watch— The Woman's Watch, 1995-1996 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 15)
  - International Women's Rights Action Watch— The Woman's Watch, 1997-1999 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 16)
  - John Birch Society (clippings), 1961-1966; Undated (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 17)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government, 1997 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 18)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government—Bulletin, 1998 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 19)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government—Bulletin Update, 2000 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 20)
  - John F. Kennedy School of Government—Women in the Lead, 2000 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 21)
  - The Kaiser Family Foundation—Kaiser Commission on Medicaid and the Uninsured, 1998 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 22)
  - The Kaiser Family Foundation—"National Survey of Small Businesses", 2002 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 23)
  - Kellog Foundation, Devolution Initiative, 1996 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 24)
  - LaGuardia Public Life Training Center, 1990-1991 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 25)
  - Legislative Women's Caucus Inc. of New York State, 1990-1992 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 26)
  - Manhattan Institute for Policy Research, 1980-1987 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 27)
  - Manhattan Institute for Policy Research—Miscellaneous Information, 1987-1993 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 28)
  - Marymount Manhattan College, 1981-1985 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 29)
  - Marymount Manhattan College—Course Schedule, 1982 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 30)
  - Media Studies Center, 1996 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 31)
  - NARAL "Who decides? A State by State Review of Abortion Rights in America", 1989 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 32)
  - National Audobon Society—"Population and Habitat in the New Millennium", Undated (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 33)
  - National Coalition for Women's Enterprise, 1989; Undated (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 34)
  - The National Committee for Public Education and Religious Liberty, 1996 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 35)
  - National Council for Research on Women—"Who's Where and Doing What", 1996 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 36)
  - The National Council for Research on Women—"A Woman's Mailing List Directory", 1990 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 37)
  - National Council for Research on Women— Women's Research Network News, 1988-1991 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 38)
  - National Gay Task Force, 1977; Undated (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 39)
  - National Organization for Women, 1992-1997; Undated (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 40)
  - National Organization for Women—Legal Defense and Education Fund, 2001 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 41)
  - National Women's Education Fund, 1980-1988; Undated (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 42)
  - National Women's Education Fund, 1981 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 43)
  - National Women's Education Fund, 1987-1989 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 44)
  - National Women's Education Fund—"A Guide to Building Bridges Between Elected and Management Women in Local Governments", 1981 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 45)
  - National Women's Education Fund—Board, 1981 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 46-48)
  - National Women's Education Fund—Board, 1984-1985 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 49)
  - National Women's Education Fund—Board Meeting, 1982 November 05-1982 November 06 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 50)
  - National Women's Education Fund—Delta Queen, 1986 (Box 4 (9-Organizations), Folder 51)
  - National Women's Education Fund—Gayle Melich Files, Undated (Cd 1)
  - National Women's Education Fund—General Information, 1986-1988 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 1)
  - National Women's Education Fund (Information for 1984), Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 2)
  - National Women's Education Fund—Misc., 1984-1985 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 3)
  - National Women's Education Fund—Organization Information, Board Meeting, 1982; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 4)
  - National Women's Education Fund—Training Group for Women in Public Life, 1982; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 5)
  - National Women's Education Fund—Women in Public Leadership Partnership, 1983 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 6)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 7)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, 1991-1994 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 8)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, 1997 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 9)
  - National Women's Political Caucus—Coalition for Women's Appointments, 1988 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 10)
  - National Women's Political Caucus—Conference, 1987; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 11)
  - National Women's Political Caucus—General Information, 1985-1989; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 12)
  - National Women's Political Caucus—Women & Politics, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 13)
  - New York Affairs—"The New Politics of Less", 1975 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 14)
  - New York City Campaign Finance Board, 1990-1993 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 15)
  - New York City commission on Human Rights, 1997-1998 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 16)
  - New York City Council, 1989-1993; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 17)
  - New York City Independent Budget Office, 1996-2000; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 18)
  - New York City Independent Budget Office—"New York City's Fiscal Outlook", 1998 January (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 19)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1968-1969; 1972 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 20)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1975 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 21)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union Biennial Report, 1997-1998 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 22)
  - New York Commission on the Status of Women—NYC Directory, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 23)
  - New York League of Conservation Voters, 1999 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 24)
  - New York League of Conservation Users Education Fund, 1993-1999; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 25)
  - New York State Assembly Task Force on Women's Issues, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 26)
  - New York State Assembly Task Force on Women's Issues, 1989-1991 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 27)
  - New York State Association of Women Officeholders, 1986-1987 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 28)
  - New York State Division for Women, 1986-1999; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 29-30)
  - New York Women's Agenda, 1993-1996 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 31)
  - The New York Women's Foundation, 1997-1999 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 32)
  - New York Women's Lobby, 1974; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 33)
  - New York Women's Lobby, 1975 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 34)
  - New York Young Republican's Club, 1959; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 35)
  - New York Young Republican's Club, 1960-1962 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 36)
  - New York Young Republican's Club, 1963-1965 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 37)
  - Nonprofit Coordinating Committee of New York, 1991-1993 (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 38)
  - Older Women's League, Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 39)
  - OMB Watch, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 5 (9-Organizations), Folder 40)
  - People for the American Way—General Information Relating to Initiatives, 1982-1996; Undated (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 1-2)
  - People for the American Way—"Government by Litmus Test: George Bush, The Far Right, and Abortion", Undated (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 3)
  - People for the American Way—Right-Wing Watch, 1991-1994 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 4)
  - The Pew Research Center, 1997-1998 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 5)
  - Planned Parenthood—Dutchess-Ulster Counties STOPP ("Stop Planned Parenthood") Reaction, 1991 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 6)
  - Planned Parenthood—Fighting STOPP, 1991 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 7-8)
  - Planned Parenthood—Lawsuit, 1987-1988 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 9-10)
  - Planned Parenthood—STOPP Conference in Poughkeepsie, 1990 (Cassette 1-9)
  - Planned Parenthood Reports, 1991 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 11)
  - Planned Parenthood Reports, 1997; Undated (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 12)
  - Political Science Quarterly, 1967 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 13)
  - Population Action International—Reports and Updates, 1993-1997 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 14)
  - Population Action International—Various Reports, 1997 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 15)
  - Population Action International—"Why Population Matters", 1996 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 16)
  - Population Crisis Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 17-18)
  - Population Crisis Committee—"International Human Suffering Index", 1987 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 19)
  - Population Crisis Committee Legislative Update, 1991 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 20)
  - Public Agenda Foundation—Report "America's Agenda" and Misc. Information, 1980-1998 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 21)
  - The Public Concern Foundation, Inc.—"The Washington Spectator," Vol. 16 No. 3-21, 1990 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 22)
  - Radcliffe Intellectual Renewal for Leaders—"Seminar Participants March 1998-April 2002", 1998 March-2002 April (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 23)
  - Radcliffe Intellectual Renewal for Leaders—Seminar Information and Notes, 1989 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 24)
  - Report on the Commission on the Causes and Preservation of Civil Disorder, 1969 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 25)
  - The Reproductive Health Technologies Project—Review of Programs, 1995-1996 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 26)
  - Sister Fund—Sister Says and Report, 1995-1997; Undated (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 27)
  - The Sister Fund—"The Struggle for Justice: A Spiritual Quest Special Report", 2000 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 28)
  - Students Organizing Students, 1990-1991 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 29)
  - Subcommittee on Foreign Relations, U.S. Senate—"Strategic and Foreign Policy Implications of ABM Systems", 1969 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 30)
  - Third Wave Fund, 1996; Undated (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 31)
  - UNIFEM, Annual Report, 2001 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 32)
  - United Press International—Promotion for Political Action Committees, 1990 (Box 6 (9-Organizations), Folder 33)
  - United States Committee for UNIFEM, 1987-1996; Undated (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 1)
  - United States Department of Labor, Women's Bureau "Flexible Lifestyles: A Look at contingent Labor", 1988 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 2)
  - United States Office of Personnel Management—"Comparable Youth for Federal Jobs", 1987 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 3)
  - Washington Institute for Women in Politics, 1975 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 4)
  - We Do—News & Views, 1989-1993 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 5)
  - We Do—News & Views, 1995-1996 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 6)
  - We Do—News &Views, 1997-2000 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 7)
  - Wings of Change Foundation—"Women and the Economy", 2003 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 8)
  - Women's Campaign Fund, 1985-1994 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 9)
  - Women's Environment & Development Organization, 1993 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 10)
  - Women's Equity Action League, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 11)
  - Women's Institute for Freedom of the Press—"Directory of Women's Media", 1979 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 12)
  - Women's Institute for Freedom of the Press—"Media Report to Women," Vol. 8 No. 9-12, Vol. 9 No. 3-6, 1980-1981 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 13)
  - Women's International Leadership Program, 1994-1999 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 14-15)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1985-1986 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 16)
  - Women's Policy, Inc.—Congress Updates and Quarterly Update Vol. 2, vol. 3, 1998-1999 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 17)
  - Women's Policy, Inc.— Quarterly Update Vol. 4, 2000 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 18)
  - Women's Policy, Inc.— Quarterly Update Vol. 4, Vol. 5, 2000-2001 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 19)
  - Women's Policy, Inc.—"Women's Health Legislation in the 106th Congress: 1999-2000", 2001 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 20)
  - Women's Resource Center of Manhattan, 1992-1995 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 21)
  - World Food Programme—"Reaching the Hungry" and "Annual Report", 1996; 1998 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 22)
  - WPOP—"Breaking the Glass Ceiling," Pat Atkinson, 1991 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Cassette 11)
  - WYNC, 2000; 2002 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 23)
  - Yankelovich, Skelly, and White, Inc. "The Mushiness Index: A Refinement in Public Policy Polling Techniques", 1981 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 24)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, Undated (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 25)
  - Young Americans for Freedom, 1961-1965 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 26)
  - Young Americans For Freedom, 1966-1969 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 27)
  - Young Americans for Freedom The New Guard, 1964-1965 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 28)
  - Young Americans for Freedom The New Guard, 1965 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 29)
  - Young Americans for Freedom The New Guard, 1966 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 30-31)
  - Young Americans for Freedom The New Guard, 1967 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 32)
  - Young Republican National Federation, Undated (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 33)
  - Young Republican National Federation, 1958-1963 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 34)
  - Young Republican National Federation, 1964-1965 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 35)
  - Young Republican National Federation, 1967 (Box 7 (9-Organizations), Folder 36-37)
  - Young Republican National Federation—Newspaper Clippings, 1967 (Box 8 (9-Organizations), Folder 1)
  - Young Republicans of California, 1961-1963 (Box 8 (9-Organizations), Folder 2)
  - Young Republicans of California, 1963-1964 (Box 8 (9-Organizations), Folder 3)
- Subject Files, 1944-2017; Undated; 10; 10.4 cubic ft.
  These files include publications, notes, flyers, news clippings, correspondence, and other items related to political and social topics, including affirmative action, civil rights, New York State government, New York State legislation regarding women, political campaigns, economic development, repeal of the draft, Vietnam, Cold War and many others. There are materials relating specifically to the Equal Rights Amendment and the attempt (and ultimate failure) to pass it. In 1980 Melich was chosen to be a fellow at Harvard, and conducted research on the impact of technology on broadcasting. Her research is included in this series, and contains scholarly articles, newspaper and magazine articles, reports, and a variety of other information. Some of the folders for the series contain newspaper clippings. Researchers may also want to look at the Organizations series which includes additional materials related to a variety of these subjects.
  Please see the Women's Advocacy series for additional files related to women's social and political rights.
  - 2001-Pre 9/11 (Misc., Although Primarily Women) (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)